welcome again to the natatorium one
major topic of conversation who can stop
the all-conquering Chinese from storming
their way to another clean sweep of
Youth Olympic titles mind you that's the
usual question of the major diving
events especially when these superb
Chinese divers have a home crowd behind
them it's the women's 3-meter
springboard preliminary today Nanjing
over local hero Wu shaping is back in
the pool again ten meter goal already
proudly on display at home perhaps the
family will need a big trophy cabinet
the teenager performed like a dream
seven other female athletes from that
platform competition are also back in
action including the silver and bronze
medalists well day to sort young how
leading to produce his impressive best
to win the men's title at this height so
the double-double as in Singapore four
years ago is still on the cards
reminder of the format here at the
Olympic Games for the women's 3-meter
springboard nine realms of diving in the
preliminary competition first five
rounds have a limited degree of
difficulty totaling nine point five
their comparatively straight full of
dives and the marks gained here are
carried through into the final then
there are four more rounds where there
is no limits on the degree of difficulty
the final will be over four ounce of
dives again without limit so this
morning counts these are the judges is
to reminder again of the way the scoring
that works seven judges the two highest
and two lowest marks are discounted the
remaining three marks are added together
and multiplied by the degrees of
difficulty for these so given to each
dive here is the dive order these divers
like Lindahl and balata and Schneider
are competing for the first time here
vivianne bath as well from Switzerland
the rest have got a feel of the
competition motivation or perhaps have a
bit of ground to make
I've been here for about an hour and a
half
preparing going through their routines
one or two drivers who are competing
tomorrow also taking advantage of the
session times I went down to those there
were a few minutes beforehand
stretching rehearsing you'll see there
the moon's going through them in their
mind for teenagers and teenagers the
world over sitting there of their
smartphones quick text message home to
mom and dad and just like the teenagers
in the crowd aren't they doing exactly
the same thing it like a mobile phone
here in China I've got to say
we have been
clearly encouraging so-called savings to
success as well here in
years from the posted major events
right from the Beijing Olympics of
course to achieve the
woke up recently which will
Shanghai they've had regular
competitions here in Beijing 2008 and
won seven out of eight golds 2011 each
Shanghai World Championships 10 out of
10 Gold's the many last month's World
Cup so let's enjoy the show that's the
most important thing
Zara Karolina the sole point
see that's holy 17-year old
that's how I D opening go
hello close launch lick 18 year old from
Kiev 7 10 meters
so you going
nice height for board there
very nice entry position as well from
the Ukrainian 27:16 nice start
damn oje great 10-meter competition
silver medal
very relaxed elegant style
clean start that is
28:40
Veronica Linda in Sweden makes her first
appearance at these games in would one
half somersault piked
but a lot of springboard drivers like to
open their church you aware that if we
died just kids hurt people for the board
even though they've been practicing in
the warmup period time ID start as well
27:25 2.1 there lotta there's
competition as well
it's a bit heavy in the end 80 year old
Italian girl
wonderheart somersault spring faint we
could have been a bit tidier
first appearance tuned for Josephine
Schneider from Germany
17 years of age
there's a nice entry
switching for 10
young Bobby Carson from candidate 16
next month
we finished 11th out of 11 at 10 meters
quite a tough competition good to see
her back and up for it again from 17
cents not a bad stock now here comes the
ten meter champion she was
the crowd is so enthusiastic for their
own local girl that it's very hard for
the judges to put back to one side but
she doesn't really give you too much to
criticize
2920 good start
alakay Adolfo Rosa from Mexico Brahms at
10 meters
she took a little while to get into her
stride on the platform but came through
in the end - showing her pedigree as an
Olympic silver medalist in the synchro
event 36
de Oliveira from Brazil fact I've hiked
1.8
making out for the water there
I'll tell the reason enjoy
Lydian bath from Switzerland her first
event of the games
judges prefer it if you can keep as
tight to the board as possible not
diving too far out into the pool 23 60
Krisha maiden from the holy forward won
the heart somersault for the
american-built
just a little heavy on entry from newton
massachusetts position actually she
poured a lower-body right through the
water 36 points
well then we're gonna feel for the
competition Veronica lindahl in factor
2.1 tariffs opening dive fen at the top
of the pack
not a big spread of marks of 15 in fact
in sessions a day here in the diving
pool
around 2:00
just another reminder these marks carry
forward that was really significant in
the Midlands 3-meter springboard there's
a bit of pressure on the leader he came
into the final the 15 points or so
advantage and that in the end was too
big to catch up so this really does
count
there is Beltran of Columbia two point
one the degree of difficulty inward
one-and-a-half somersault
not a great line into the water 4095
home for more from that Terry
got a close loss lick of Ukraine
three European Junior Championship
medals so she knows how to put a routine
together in with one half somersault two
point one
two point one is the highest DD that
girls have thoughts in this opening five
rounds look to make the most of it
27:24 X and then a half that's too bad
Oh je very nice again
I'm trying to emulate a panda Leila
relog we've got Tim Silver's four years
ago in Singapore setting off on the
right road to achieving that 1540
domenica link down
she's got college program ahead of that
is the 13.0 dive into our routine which
needs to get these first ones out the
way trying to keep the legs upright on
the way through 32 points
Laura balata of Italy 18 year old from
cosenza as a back dive pike
comes into this competition in confident
form having won the European Hughley
Championships won meters 781 metre of
course not an Olympic event
Josephine
second after the opening round visitor
hi Terry
that forward one and a half somersaults
is only one point six
nice hiked position it's a little bit of
impact from the heels on the water on
g-spot 733 60
now Molly Carlson
back dive point
not sixteen till next month looking for
more consistent performance about 10
meters all she's smiling anyway 37 80
she's so cool before she dives total
concentration move jumping in homicide
this is a 2.1
what made twice as good a job in fact as
we've come to expect
elegant through the air but the entry
was below her normal standard 44:10
three sevens that might just stop
opponents from becoming too intimidated
every diner is capable of just sitting
up here and there
reverse dive is at 1.9
40 84 in the 70s at seven-and-a-half de
Oliveira nice tidy opening dive forward
1/2 sand so
a little bit heavy on the entry
reaching out from the water is not
holding port is straighter line and
entry its 3360 en parte this is a 2.1
dive for the swisco
again it's an entry which creates such a
strong impression 43056 and-a-half air
pressure laden Mahoney
if you wanna World Junior Championships
this fight in 2012
that dive is worth one point eight
fairly solid job there and seven of the
hearts
although je leading the pack at the
moment from Shaitan ping just a few
points back there some work to do for
these remaining girls
have you divert trying to find their own
way of just isolating themselves from
the pressure got a lot listen to music
we need headphones and go off into their
own little world
nine rounds is a long stint for them
I told them started to struggle towards
the end of the competition of just
keeping their form going right through
the whole program there is Beltran
seemed to collapse almost into the water
at the end of entry
just see the cars come down and hit the
water there 6.5
together as law slick of Ukraine
back then I've liked
if you can get through these limited
people who have difficulty dives nice
and cleanly you can put herself in a
position to launch an attack for a medal
two eights there is encouraging 42/30
very well
now hello je really is making an
impression leading a competition it's
really the first followed rounds that's
the competition within a competition
back dive 1.8
when these time is dripping songs into a
strong position then find out we deal
with a little bit more expectation and
maybe that's come through a bit of that
dive because it's down in the 60s
34:20
Veronica Lindo from Sweden
ranked fourth after two dives back
though
nineteen old is the Swedish national
champion
competing at senior level last year just
a little bit untidy on the entry there
keeps her down at 36
Laura
balata not really got going so far
since top European Junior Championship
medals three meters synchronized an
individual so she's been expecting more
three seven thirty nine ninety a bit
better
so as a team Schneider from Germany
again the that guy hiked
needs a bit more work 3420
fifteen-year-old Molly Carlson
this is a big experience for
the young diver from Thunder Bay she
works on her own out there with a coach
of course but away from the rest of the
national squad who are all based in
Quebec does it make it any easier that's
a better dive for team of Haiti
now you chain Kulii
by her standards instead get back on
track the back dive piked
is worth one point eight
right back in the greens I would think
lovely position there look at that entry
could be flawless that just in case you
were worried about a stop
forty-eight sixty three nines
I lost Oh what's up from Mexico
she became quite a star after London
2012 when she was just 15 years of age
alongside Paola Espinosa winning a
silver 1450 Oliveira from Brazil
but really showing her best form so far
this is a 10.1 difficulty
don't you seem to give it plenty of
attack
she's lost a little bit of control on
entry
down in the six points 1495
vivianne part of Switzerland
nothing massively rolling without really
impressing too much 36 points
pressure laden Mahoney
back in 8
we won the bronze in the qualifier in
Monterey back in March so would have
come to Nanjing here the reasonable
amount of optimism not totally hits no
straps here
forty 85
that's that third superb dive has got
woo Shaitan ping back up to the top of
the table
and lo GE just slipping back a little
bit
Molly Carlson the youngster getting some
encouragement moving up the leaderboard
and keep them moving ready to go all the
time so the competition gets a real and
momentum to it
today's peltro starts round 4
reverse dive height
entry just a little heavy
25:15
18 year old Ukrainian going very
steadily as a reverse dive here piked
needs to keep this up
so be looking nicely consistent
is what it's all about and sparks
carried forward needs to get herself in
a good position to keep progressing in
the final 20 85 that's another steady
effort no je just slipping back that's a
lot nicer
very slim sleek style
very good 3/8 2560 that's back on track
Lindau the Swedish girl
now it's just a bit heavy as well
she's competed a few wrong trees over
the last few years
fairly selectively but good experience
done better in the synchro events 35:15
there
Nora DeLaughter
big hero tonio Kenyatta surprisingly
championship silver medalist
nice looking to get her confidence going
Spike's of position decent entry as well
it's definitely gets her sevens down to
Josefin Schneider
didn't really go herself set for the
entry into the water
top half of the dive look nice just
didn't really complete it all the way
thirty eight points
Molly Carlson has made a bit of progress
two point one the turret here not a
chance for movement at the table
she's proving pretty steady now three
sevens
44:10 keep the disasters at bay and
yours give yourself as a chance
the atmosphere lifts for the 10 meter
champion on the spring board especially
after that simple
I would take too much notice of the
crowd though that's a very nice effort
yes
46 55 it's just a temporary little
glitch by her sky high standards
and off go a lot up from Mexico
this again is worth two point one
she doesn't seem to get too much wrong
with her dives very consistent in
Piketon position that probably makes a
very reliable synchro partner
people just keep the scores rattling
along really does give you a boost just
waiting for her
sevens 44:10 de Oliveira progressing a
bit up to seventh
no she's got a finger ranking 30 at 10
meters now on the springboard she just
held it a little bit longer through the
entry all the way through it needs to go
3895 Riviera fast another thing to look
for it's just where the divers complete
their hurdle that final step watch the
end of the board you need to be that's a
good position the entry was one of our
angle but there is a sweet spot
on the ball that they try to hit and get
the maximum launch
to six point five and a seven for
thirty-eight
raesha lady mahoney completes the fourth
round for the amount of one half
somersault
and she was packing forth and looking to
maintain that sort of position
don't clearing mistakes there
for looking for ten just sevens
four rounds gone wrong Shan ping has got
a 10-point lead to carry into tonight at
the moment with one more round of these
limited dives to go
this is a beautiful building the divers
have been saying how much they've
enjoyed the facilities here in Nanjing
part of this impressive Olympic sports
center complex for a right next door to
the main stadium you can see that
adjustment there that wheel affects the
tension on the board particularly
relevant for some of the men will have a
bigger variation in weight
now this is the last round of the five
rounds which will be carried forward to
the final phase belt road of Columbia
he's back marker at the moment 17-year
old
just down there in the six fives for 39
points he's in potential bronze medal
position very important that she
completes this forward one-half
somersault on the twist successfully
and she seems to have done that
Balian coach looks pleased
okay loan major issues 44:10
and in the silver medal position no je
the silver medalist from the ten meters
10:01 half somersault with half a twist
myself in a strong position to really be
up there competing in the final 45
points
you wanna kill him down
Oh Sam I saw one twist 2.1
eighteen years of age much taller more
powerful figure in comparison to say the
Malaysian girl it's my chance to get
some real impact on the board but you
still want to control it twenty-nine
five four three six point five
mulatto has improved as the rounds of
progressed through
a bit more success at 1 meter but
starting to show now what she can do on
a springboard
44:10 from three sevens
Josephine Schneider from Germany this
one and a half somersault with half a
twist again as a two point one tariff
die
he's competed at European junior and
world Juliet championship level but not
till this year and she made an impact
when she got a bronze of the one meter
22 points they're still the light side
very Tolson
once you had shown signs of finding a
little bit of forms
needs to keep her confidence up being so
experienced a little bit below par again
giving 5990 Jing ping mistakes on this
her last dive will carry into the final
forward one-half somersault one twist
two point one roots of appreciation not
surprisingly from fans
great height and control very relaxed
entry lovely completion to that dive
very nice indeed
and again setting all the standards with
5460 that is a big points pool
who's having to follow the home favorite
it's never easy because commit to her
dives gets plenty of elevation reacting
out intimidating performance from will
shame ping she has got plenty of
experience herself remember will be 725
doing the job
agreed the Oliveira
back down in eighth place
in word wonderful so solid very clean
entry there hardly a sound
talk about the grip on entry but its
surface on the more in evidence and you
get to the bigger men on the platform
but you still get that same clean sound
when the dive is successful still only
sevens and 7.5 s 445 15
the Swiss representative did the end of
rather resigned look up what that ones
and
encouragement there in the applause
because I don't think the entry was
everything she made she made something
out of the dive there you can do a lot
of work under the water and make sure
you hold it so she did well to get 42
points there
so the final dive of the five rounds
that will be carried forward
raesha laden from the Honi ranked fourth
mistakes here
two point one
kept quite relaxed through the air
arms down punching the whole nice
upright entry
at least seventies from the judges there
was a 600 name it seems a little bit
harsh but they are the experts
well these compositions that will go
forward to the final then China Malaysia
Ukraine Mexico
and the competitors at the bottom a
little bit of a disadvantage now
look at the mold
headphones to the ready
what we did twenty years ago in darling
they didn't have all these distractions
it's all about keeping the concentration
going though mainly just divorcing
yourself from the pressures this is a
big spotlight for these teenagers
competing junior events yes but this one
with all the extra crowds television
coverage and that magical word and then
pick around them eggs now a lot more
complex certainly get the crowd even
more involved
up to 2.4 about forward two and a half
somersault
execution dark still comparatively low
Claire's lost leg should be very keen to
get through these drives which have to
repeat we can change them but would be
unexpected or enlarged
just as well it is the preliminary
competition because if that dive goes as
well as that then
to be in trouble it's a 3.0 tariff which
is towards the high end in this
competition anyway and it didn't go at
all to blame 3450 that can't happen in
the blind
again though je has a 3.0 tariff dive
was interesting where they position them
in the program so it's likely she'll
start with this even their home fans
quick to acknowledge she's a very clever
look how tight that comic is my spin
speed entry seemed okay the judge is
quite conservative there 7.5 but it
consistently so
you really could dig dull
you can't expect to see more going wrong
now that the dives have become a lot
more involved
this is another one of those 3.0 degree
of difficulty dives and again she came
up a bit short they're not really having
the room to get the legs up right 48
points
Laura balata made some progress after
less than glorious start with three and
a half somersault with
or the Tuck position always looks a bit
more fast and furious in the pike
knees up as far as possible going to go
grip on those legs
mr. number six follows 5460
Josefin Schneider getting back in 10th
place for the 17 year old German diver
that was pretty tidy
maybe not point so from babba angle
remember the judges just get a one look
and they didn't like it that much
51 13
fifteen-year-old Molly Carlson
in the teal Hassan assault 2.7 well this
is all a big learning experience for her
struggling to
keep the major mistakes out of her dives
and he can just see the complete over
rotation there the slapping the water in
the back of their legs while she's
dealing with it mentally pretty well
have you seen a coach they're keeping
morale
now showing up in England to Lahav
somersault tucked 2.7 she's not that
complex routine of dives she just does
them awfully well
terrific spin speed
big league
out into the entry position pretty well
holding the shape without being ramrod
straight 6480
said well completed dive
and off cone lawsuit after the Lord
Mayor's Show or the Mexican again that
sense of an attack from the Olympic
synchro silver medalist
just a fair angle on that entry position
56 points
Ingrid de Oliveira she's got for quite
ambitious dives 33.0 s including this
one and a 3.1
it's a considerably higher tariff
schedule compared to say little
champagne it's all about how
successfully you complete them very good
tight tight position there but the legs
just pulling over bit on entry 51
Switzerland's Livia and Bart
they moved to an evolve somersault
seem to get herself a bit cramped up in
that
we really got opened out nice and
straight
pretty sure Layden Mahoney
linked
v after those limited dives that
carry-forward
see what she's got in the unrestricted
section
he would sell basalt 2.7
she's got a 3.0 dive in her repertoire
so she needs to execute the world again
the lakes just holding away on entry
they're down in the 65 50 to 65
so now these final four rounds are
primarily there to decide the evenings
dive order whooshing ping set to die
blast Paris Beltran at the moment to die
first they reverse it of course
to the half thousand
about the capacity here in the left--it
or IAM obviously the seating spring all
the way along the pool diving fall right
next to the swimming pool
splendid facility
one of the big competitions are held
outdoors
Shanghai for example the left--it Orion
there is fantastic outdoor facility you
do have though variations of course for
climates and you get indoors
there is no trend of Columbia two and a
half somersault
again didn't really seem to get
straightened out completely coming out
of that position and again the over
rotation
like that at all 3375 has lost leg from
Ukraine
2.40 after that big 3.0 in the previous
round
and has completed it a bit more
successfully
maybe then she could have been a bit
more vertical
could work through the air that don't
leave divided up into different sections
remember there was a good takeoff 75154
points
no je from Malaysia ranked second full
with her and a half summer soul very
quick at her rotations means she needs a
lot of core strength
to put on the brakes she didn't quite
manage that there
5460 what a bit better than that when it
comes to the big final
Veronica lindau from Sweden
in assault
it looks like another example in fact
over-rotation
trolling somersaults and you can see
always falling away into the water there
pelota
forward 2012 somersault one twist 3.0
just about to say cheese
but more impressive as the competition
has caught on but that became very
untidy we got into a great position
through the air and the entry not great
either fides 45 there another day
perhaps Joseph in slide up
not two and a half summer soldier
strong figure on the board there is
there a chance to get freddied elevation
but great control in that dive 53:20
multicolored
which is having quite a test to hold her
they're learning routine together
or complete disaster that 46:18
here comes the favorite total of the
crowd the bookmakers so to speak you've
shown ping back two and a half
somersault
well again showing a bit of fail ability
and that my her spellers is close to
disastrous 4480 to see competitions one
light excellent not because somebody
made mistakes or failed to justify
themselves but everyone is palpable we
would be one of the diners who might
profit if the bed and favorite had a
disappointing final evening
but she too has got to perform as well
and didn't totally in that dive
Ingrid de Oliveira performed three and a
half somersault piked 3.1 says people
dive and thus we get in this competition
well because her program is that bit
more ambitious if she doesn't get it
right she will get reasonable points
from it but again that over-rotating was
untidy when she's down in the five cards
51:15
helium Bart this is a more modest two
point four forward two and a half
somersault slapping the water with their
heels as she came in
just running over there towards our can
review 39 65 fives
cumberly's marks do not count this
evening
raesha Layden Mahoney
Oh
going into this round so she will have
thoughts of medals if she can find her
best form and that wasn't it
really do have to cut out the disasters
if you're going to be up there on the
bed on stage you can't be brilliant all
the time by the same token you can't
afford to be getting four fives and
fives if you've got a hope of getting
there on the podium
whooshing ping from low GI and aloft
girl offered they look with three
pedigree divers and the spread widening
all the time
Monte Carlson the youngest diver there
in 11th
two more rounds to go again
you have to repeat that nine rounds is
quite an extended competition
normally a Olympic all World
Championship of all when you get fields
in 1450 divers you have a preliminary
round which will Whittle them down to 18
for a semi final and then 12 for a final
these divers are guaranteed second
attempt in the final with these first
five rounds carrying over as we keep
emphasizing arrays Beltran Colombia
then you can afford to get the mistakes
out of your system if you like
and that one didn't go to plan at all
4.5
these games are such a fantastic
experience for these comparatively
inexperienced competitors
or event has a real big-time feel about
it
got a Fresno slick his fifth you know
she can produce a full round of
unlimited IDEs come the final she could
be in the chance but again she's not
really delivered with this effort it's a
poor entry and will be marked down
accordingly in the fours
33:16
je needs to keep her confidence and her
consistency hi solutely no doubt she's
got the talent
back two and a half somersault driving
in malaysia has made such progress the
silver medalist and elena renown from
four years ago has been a real
trailblazer for first the girls and more
recently the men in malaysian diving
that one not one of her better efforts
to follow the consistency in the final
veronica lynn down
back two and a half summer so
make a nice sound on entry even though
the feet are falling away a bit there
58 80
DeLaughter blowing a little hot and cold
through this competition reverse
two-and-a-half somersault 10.8 a good
takeoff position they're moving to get
as close to the end in the board as
possible about final hurdle as they call
it
doing a decent job of holding her
position 13:37 5818 Josephine Schneider
it's where we are Nanjing 2014 this to
enhance somersault
another 3.0 dive ends with two stronger
guys will always give her a chance she
needs to really get them all right 58.50
okay
he calls and the fifteen-year-old from
Thunder Bay always with the very young
competitors
started off decently that died again at
the Chester mountains getting the entry
position
through the rotations not really getting
up right
you know this is a young person's sport
she still in a very early stage 42
points
miss the applause for Wu Shan ping 2.8
nothing over-ambitious with this with
this two and a half somersault
well really enjoying having a local
favorite to get behind
inter-country limited to just one
entrant even though China would be
capable of finding what more the ability
to hold their own at this level 6720
good eights there
I'm off the law that this would be a
bronze medal position for her when is
the final back two and a half somersault
two point eight
it's a little bit too offline there
remember the judges only get the side on
view from our camera shows ten different
aspects but still no doubt there was a
bit of a slap of the feet on entry
fifty-eight eighty though your voids
disasters you always get something out
of each dive
every day on it that up
for at the moment so she's definitely
looking up looking back in the
competition
again another attacking die she was in
the platform event
just loses a bit of neatness and he goes
for it 5550
Fabian Bart
she's ranked tenth after seven rounds
our previous dive was very short in
terms of points that's better but not
buying loads still down in the fives 42
points Felicia she could find better
form when it comes to the final racial
Aden Mowgli also had a disappointing
last dive always good to see if they
could put a poor dive behind them and
come back fighting reverse
two-and-a-half somersault tucked this is
2.8 go from Massachusetts
one of the former gymnasts in this
competition a bit below par all the way
through that 49
one round to go whooshing ping well that
what a lot really changing too much law
and DeLaughter has really made great
progress and you think that some of
those in the second half of the table
have more to show
the competitors always get to the call
with hour and a half more plus the
traveling down from the village to
prepare so I have to sustain their
concentration right the way through or
around about three hours three and a
half hours means an early start for them
as well
I'm going to have the test as well as to
how to handle the time between a
preliminary and a final bit of rest
analyze what they've done not worry too
much
there is Beltran final dive to this
preliminary
she's doing the water a bit of a smack
there on intrigue reverse two-and-a-half
somersault 2.8 was the intention
losing control 3220
got a close colleague has seen a couple
of her dives in this final section of
four go fairly arrive but at other times
has looked to have real potential
there's two and a half somersault tucks
2.8 that was definitely one of her
better ones
he thinks he's one of the competitors
may start a bit down the order but who
could come strollin meld to challenge if
she finds her best form 60 20 the better
note from which to finish we know loans
ie
really looked the part
she's still second half somersault one
the half twists this is just a two point
for Terry interestingly she started
these last four rounds when three point
zero two two eight so they're ending
with a two four
dollars per purchase preferred to go the
other way and leave their big dives till
the end when they can maybe make up
ground but 50 40 is her points hall so
it's an interesting tactic
we can dig down
she certainly commits to her dives to be
tentative off that board
just could do a little bit more neatness
all the way through 44 33 40
now Laura balata it's been very
impressive the way she's steadily moved
her way up the field European Julia one
meter champion and now we're seeing
exactly where that medal winning form
really came from back to a half
somersault
1 below par dive of the previous 3 at
one like a second
and she's also shown that she can really
produce some nice scores 4340 she'll
work better
Josefin Schneider as well
there's performed some decent looking
dives in this second half of the
competition forward two and a half
somersault with one twist three with
zero to finish
Jiro's 23.0 dives at the end of her
program which means she can make an
impact but of course he's got a gunman
right that one was a bit off the mark
he Carlson for fifteen-year-old youngest
diver at the games
there's two and a half somersault again
won't really get herself into the right
position to make a good clean entry
through those somersaults and you can
see she just can't get enough space
coming up consistently short 3780 I
think like your attitude those things to
bounce out of it
Pingping will want to leave her rivals
with a bit of a reminder a lot of them
in fact in modern taping or their
shoulders just to keep the muscles held
in the right position back 1/2
somersault one half twists get it's just
2.4
turning the applause lets you know that
she has completed her dive there was
hardly it sound the light on the board
from the entry was clean earthly
proverbial
and a nice set of marks there a nine two
lines one three the lines one discounted
6214 I can divert orosco lava
let's put myself into a silver medal
position as it were definitely going to
be right up there in medal contention
you need two and a half somersault to
finish
guarantee keeps rattling out the scores
in dazzling the 5655 1538 18 very very
consistent
they scored just a little bit below that
but still 1565 no disasters at all
Ingrid de Oliveira is also progressed in
this competition
back to another soul 3.0
came up well short
to get through those somersaults clear
enough to give yourself the time to
those legs right up into a good entry
position but not that time 3450
pion Bart back 1/2 somersault one half
twists 2.4
since back in 10th place
she's only competing up to three meters
there was the team event still to come
the lineups for that will be so this is
a very big day for her again the entry
was well angled 3960 will better form in
the final completing the preliminary
competition galicia laden the holy of
the united states she has a reverse one
and a half somersault two and a half
twists
and that is the concluding dive of this
preliminary competition she will want to
end on a high note
not totally achieved it with that dive
entry just a little untidy and the
judges lead out in the 6.5 son a 6-4 55
this is how the standings look after
their preliminary competition will
shaping very much the class act the
rostral offer and low likely to battle
it out for the other medals unless one
of the others comes out of the pack with
a strong challenge all will be revealed
in the final
well that's a big morning for them
during rounds of diving they've gone
through that's been quite a test
remember the first five rounds those
scores will carry forward and that may
be of more significance from the actual
dive order which is usually the biggest
guy but we've seen what they can do
hopefully quite a few of these
supporters will be back here again for
the final hoping to see yet another
Chinese success certainly given them
every encouragement but it all comes
down to what happens on the big guide so
to speak great to see so many young
children coming out here enjoying this
sport maybe there'll be another
moonshine pink or another